得 您待着 我-我来接
Okay. I'll -- I'll get that.
喂
Hello?
喂 曼尼正在准备
Hey, Manny's getting his outfit together
他今晚舞会的行头
for the dance tonight.
我正在把舞会用品往车上装呢
I was just taking some supplies out to the car.
太激动了 小伙子们的第一次舞会耶
Isn't this exciting -- the boys' first dance?
简直是我人生中最美好的一天
Greatest day of my life.
话说菲尔有绿色的装饰方巾不
Does Phil have a green pocket square for him?
青色
Teal!
好吧 青色的
Teal.
我不知道 不过我不觉得菲尔是个
I don't know. I don't think Phil's
会往西服口袋里搞什么装饰方巾的人哎
really a pocket-square kind of a guy.
咱还是问问米奇吧
Why don't we conference in Mitch?
看 介个玩意儿行不
Ay! Look. This might work.
这是蓝绿色的诶...
Well, except that it's turquoise...
还是个胸罩
oh, and a bra?!
你觉得俺们村儿里的孩子会戴装饰方巾吗
Do you think the kids in my village had pocket squares?
又扯什么你们村儿
Here we go with the village.
-爸 还在听不 -很不幸 我还在
- Dad, are you still there? - Unfortunately, yes.
帮我问下克莱尔
Please ask Claire what time
我该几点去学校帮忙啊
do I need to be at the school to help set up.
歌洛莉亚想问--
Gloria wants to know --
不用重复 我听着了 听着了
No, I heard. I heard.
告诉她很感谢她这么热心
Um, tell her thank you so much,
但我们的人手已经足够了
but we have all the help we could possibly need,
其实如果她不想来的话
and she doesn't even have to come tonight
-她压根儿都不用出现 -克莱尔说
- if she doesn't want to. - Claire said --
我听见了
I heard.
喂
Hello?
喂 米奇
Oh, hey, Mitch!
-你在哪儿 -我们在公园呢
- Where are you? - Oh, we're at the park.
你肯定不敢相信
You would not believe
某些家长是怎么打扮自己孩子的
how some of these people dress their kids.
莉莉的小伙伴刚刚从沙坑玩具车里
Lily's friend just pulled a Britney Spears
拽出一个迷你版布兰妮
getting out of a sandbox car.
老爸也在听着呢
So, dad's on the line.
你那儿有没有青色的装饰方巾啊 曼尼要用
Do you he a teal pocket square for Manny?
小卡 曼尼想问你借青色的装饰方巾
Cam, Manny needs a teal pocket square.
我有青色的 水蓝色的 浅蓝色的
Oh, I've got teal, I've got aqua, i've got sea foam...
-小卡啥都有 -小卡有
- Yeah, Cam's got one. - Cam's got one.
太棒了
Yes!
我想起来了 我借给安德瑞了
Oh, you know what? I lent it to Andre.
不过他借给安德瑞了
Ah. He lent it to Andre.
情况有变
Flag on the play.
你说啥
What's that mean?
啥意思
What's that mean?!
看来我得去趟商场了
Now I got to go to the mall.
这身怎么样
Is this okay?
太巧了 卢克也要去商场耶
Oh, hey! Luke has to go to the mall, too.
为啥
What?
菲尔
Phil.
咱走吧 绿巨人
Let's go, Incredible Hulk.
那个叫莉莉小姑娘是你家的不
Uh, is that ur little girl over there -- Lily?
-是啊 看她多可爱 -是啊
- Yes. Look at her. - Yes.
这事说起来有点尴尬
Uh, well, this is a little bit awkward,
不过她刚刚咬了我家泰勒
but she bit Tyler.
不是吧
Oh, no.
我的老天爷
Oh, my goodness.
我真不知道该说什么好
I -- I don't even know what to say.
她从没这么干过
She's never done anything like that before.
到底怎么回事
How did it happen?
我也不知道 我没看见
I don't know. I didn't see.
大家都爱来这套
It's time to play everyone's favorite game.
"都怪基佬爸爸"
"Let's blame the gay dads"!
你知道异性恋都生出什么货色吗
You know who had straight parents?
希特勒
Adolf Hitler.
杀人狂曼森
Charles Manson.
-咱还继续不 -爱打人的超模娜奥米
- Shall we go on? - Naomi Campbell.
但我知道肯定有这么回事
I-I know it happened.
他胳膊上还有牙印呢
He's got bite marks on his arm.
老天 还真有人咬你了哈
Oh, gosh, someone really sunk their teeth into you, huh?
你真是个可口的小家伙
It's 'cause you're such a yummy little guy!
是啊
Yes!
才不是我家闺女干的呢
Our daughter didn't do that.
-但是他说 -好吧
- But he said -- - Right.
没准儿是他搞错了
He's probably just confused.
你猜我认为是谁干的
You know who I bet did it, though?
是比利 念起来和莉莉差不多
Billy. Rhymes with Lily.
而且 他可好斗了
Plus, he is very aggressive.
他家保姆就在那儿呢
His babysitter's right over there.
她 她不太会管孩子
She's -- she's not much of a disciplinarian.
我可以跟你保证
Because I can assure you,
要是我家闺女咬人了
if our child did something like this,
我们肯定会寸步不离地看着她
we would be on her like white on rice.
我知道这听起来貌似有点种族歧视
And I know that sounds a little bit like a racial slur,
因为我们是白人 而她八成爱吃米饭
because we're white and she presumably likes rice,
不过我真不是故意说成这样的
but I didn't intend it that way.
终于有车位了
Ah. Finally. There's a spot.
小伙子们 我现在好为你们骄傲
Guys, I am just bursting with pride right now.
这可是你们第一次舞会啊
Your first dance.
很快你们也成男子汉了
Soon you're gonna be men.
你们得知道 男子汉可不会
I want you to know there's more to be a man
整天想着买漂亮衣服
than just shopping for fancy outfits.
没错 很快你们就要长出胸毛
Yep. Pretty soon, you get some hair on your chest,
接电话时
you start answering the phone,
人家也不会以为你们是女人了
people don't think you're ladies.
别磨叽了 戴茜小姐
Come on, today, Miss Daisy.
事实上 戴茜小姐是坐车的
Actually, Miss Daisy was the one being driven,
不是开车的
not the one driving.
没看过
Never saw it.
那片儿叫《为戴茜小姐开车》
It's called "Driving Miss Daisy".
我说你今天话挺多啊
You got a real lip on you today. You know that?
喂 那是我们的车位
Hey! That was our spot!
你在干啥啊
What are you doing?
你就这么把车位拱手让人了啊
You're gonna let him snake your spot?
没啥大不了的
Not worth it.
孩子们 要想当男子汉
Boys, here's the only thing you got to know
你们必须得记住
about being a man --
永远不能让别人抢走你的东西
never let someone take what is yours.
除非那只是个微不足道的小车位
Unless it's just a parking spot
车位多的是嘛
and there's plenty of others.
好贴心哦 菲尔 真该把这写下来
That's sweet, Phil. You ought to write that down.
你包里肯定还带着口红呢吧 娘娘腔
You got any lipstick in your purse?
你开玩笑吗 我很爱杰的
I love Jay. Are you kidding me?
他是我的哥们
He's my boy.
当然 他经常和我过不去
Yeah, he gives me a hard time,
可这就是和岳父的相处之道
but that's the deal with a father-in-law.
关键在于
The key is,
我绝不向他妥协
I never let him see just how much it devastates me.
这念"邓菲"
It's "Dunphy."
我就这么念的 "傻菲"
That's what I said -- "Dumphy."
不对 不是"傻"
No, not "dumb".
是"邓菲"
"Dunphy".
"傻菲"
"Dumphy".
-跟我念"邓" -邓
- Say "done". - Done.
-跟我念"菲" -菲
- Say "fee". - Fee.
-"邓菲" -"傻菲"
- "Done-fee". - "Dumphy".
好的 往这边挪点
All right, just bring it this way?
这边 就这了
This way -- there it is.
很好 谢谢 很完美
Perfect. Thank you. Perfect.
克莱 克莱尔
Cla-a-aire?
-怎么了 -你能让格斯去修一下那盏灯吗
- What? - Can you ask Gus to fix that light?
我刚去请他帮忙 他却对着我大声咆哮
I asked him, but he just growled at me.
噢 天呐 好吧
Oh, gosh. Okay.
格斯 别吓唬贝瑟妮了 请你快去把灯修了吧
Gus, stop scaring Bethenny and fix the light, please?
别逼我
Don't make me come over there.
我忙得很呢 要修自己去修吧
I'm busy. You fix it.
你这样是不是就因为
Is this because I said
我不肯跟你一起跳舞
i wouldn't come to the dance with you?
格斯 我已为人妻了 别人会说闲话的
Gus, I'm a married woman. People would talk.
只要和我销魂一舞 保证你忘乎所以
One dance with me, you'd forget all about him.
好吧 有一个不肯修灯的老公已经够让我受的了
Yeah, I already have a husband who doesn't fix lights.
求你了
Please?
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
你简直就是这所学校的顶梁柱
This school would literally fall apart without you.
还说不上"顶梁柱"啦 可
Well, I don't know about "literally"，but...
大家好 我来咯
Ihola, hola! I'm here!
噢 你还是来了
Oh, you came anyway.
太好了
That's great.
我感觉也很好
I think it's great, too.
几周前 校方在征集
A few weeks ago, they asked for someone
愿意负责这次舞会的人
to be in charge of the school dance,
我报名了
and I volunteered.
学校这次召集志愿者
The school asks for volunteers
就是为了能让所有人参与其中
so that everybody will feel included,
可他们在开什么国际大玩笑
but who are they kidding?
我才是这项工作的不二人选
They want me to do it.
自从海莉十二岁开始 学校里所有的舞会都是我负责的
I've put on every school dance since Haley was 12.
这是我的专长
It's my thing.
校方让我们当联席主席
They made us co-chairs,
就是为了让我们合作
which means we're supposed to do everything together,
可克莱尔从不接受我的建议
but Claire won't take any of my ideas.
她居然提议"天方夜谭"为舞会主题
She suggested an "Arabian nights" theme.
对小孩子来说是不是太早了
Isn't it a little soon?
好吧 大伙注意了
Okay. Um, hey, everybody?
你们认识歌洛莉亚吗 曼尼的母亲
Do you know Gloria, Manny's mom?
她是来帮我们忙的
She's here to help us out today.
我是联席主席
I'm the co-chair.
两个小时以后孩子们就到了
So, the kids are gonna be here in two hours,
大伙赶紧工作吧
so everybody back to work.
Everybody back to work.
这话我说过了
I just said that.
我这是在"联说"
And I just co-said it.
那女士居然厚颜无耻的来指责莉莉
I mean, the nerve of that lady accusing Lily?
江山易改 本性难移 小卡
Mm. Well, you know what? You can't change people, Cam.
我们只能尽量不去受他们影响
I mean, we just have to rise above.
怎么了
What happened?
她咬了我一口
She bit me.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
她又咬我了
Ohh! Ah! She did it again!
这简直就是《暮光之城》
It's like "Twilight" back here!
不行 没有雪糕吃 比利
No! No ice cream for you, Billy,
因为那个阿姨说你到处咬人
because the lady say you biting!
好吧 快走 快走
Okay. Okay. Go. Go.
-好的 -快 快 快
- Yeah. - Go, go, go.
快开车
Drive.
你确定这个是青色吗
Are you sure this is teal?
因为我开始觉得这个有点偏绿色
'Cause I'm starting to get a real strong green thing here.
那是日光灯的反射效果
That's the fluorescent lights.
我可以把这个拿到灯光明亮点的地方看看吗
Do you mind if I walk this over to lamps galore?
你别老担心这个了
I need you to worry about this less.
猜猜谁正好能穿下人体模特身上的衣服
Guess who fit into the suit on the mannequin
还给我们打了八折
and saved us 20%?
我一直不明白 人体模特
Here's something I didn't know about mannequins --
怎么就没有"香肠"呢
they don't have a wiener.
那是什么鬼东西
What the heck is that?
那是"小鸡鸡"的婉转说法
It's a nicer word for "penis".
不是 我是说 这是什么鬼东西
No, I mean, what the heck is this?
领带啊
It's a tie.
可这是青色的
It's teal.
那又怎样
I don't care.
我第一眼看见就拿了
I just grabbed the first one I saw.
去拿个别的
Well, grab a different one.
不要
No!
我现在喜欢上它了
Now I like it.
我们先到的 别插队
Uh, I think we were here first.
我只买一样东西 我赶时间
I just have one thing. I'm in a big rush.
我们也赶时间
So are we.
没关系 你先结账吧
That's fine. Go ahead.
你搞什么
Seriously?
杰 这没什么大不了的
Jay, it's not a big deal.
你能帮我查一下
And can you give me the sale prices
上周我买的那些东西的价格嘛
for some things I bought last week?
噢 我滴神呐
Oh, for god's sake!
正如我说的那样
Now, this is what i'm talking about, boys.
做人要强硬 不然别人会得寸进尺
You give people an inch, they'll run all over you.
或者你也可以做个好人 让爱传递
Or you could just be nice -- pay it forward.
别老是给他们灌输不良思想
They don't make movies out of bad ideas.
我只知道你们要努力争夺自己想要的东西
All I know is you got to fight for what you want.
要是只有一个就业岗位
If there's one job available,
而你们不去争取 就会像那样被人夺走
this guy just got it,
你们就在"傻菲"家等着挨饿吧
and they go hungry at the "Dumphys'".
是"邓菲"啦
"Dunphys'".
我还是搞不懂 她干吗要咬人
Okay, I don't get it. Why is she biting?
莉莉 你干吗要咬人
Lily, why are you biting?
她才不是咬人呢 她这是在磨牙
She's not biting. She's teething.
在人身上磨牙
On people!
好了 要是她再这样继续咬她的玩伴
All right, if she starts biting her play dates,
她就会被人唾弃的
she's gonna be a pariah.
"食人鲳"也挺可爱的
Try "piranha".
你要这样称呼咱们的女儿吗 小卡
Really, cam?
一时口快
It was right there.
好吧 你也该知道我绝对
All right, you should also know that I in no way --
一点儿都没怪你
in no way -- blame you.
-那多谢了 你为啥要怪我 -我没有
- Well, thank you. Why would you blame me? - I don't.
好啊 因为我就没怪你
Well, good, because I don't blame you.
明显得很
Well, obviously.
我觉得你又在怪我了
Uh, okay, well, now I'm starting to feel the blame.
没 我没有 好吧 是因为
No. No. Don't -- it's...
整天都是你跟她在一起 你该教好她的
it's just that you're with her all day.
现在我有一个咬人的女儿和一个叮(激怒)人的老公
I have a daughter who bites and a partner who stings.
好吧 你想知道真相吗
Okay. Okay, you want to know the truth?
你有时候会给她一些奇怪的暗示
Sometimes you've sent her some mixed signals.
我要咬你的小脚丫
I'm gonna bite your feet!
我要把它们咬掉
I'm gonna bite 'em right off!
哦 我可没有把牙齿当瑞士军刀来用
Oh, I'm not the one who uses my teeth like a multi-tool.
好了 莉莉的饼干
Here we go. Cookies for Lily...
我们的酒
...and wine for us.
好吧
Okay.
我不敢相信你居然拿
I can't believe you would equate --
别把我的头咬掉了
Oh, don't bite my head off.
我可不是电池
I'm not a pack of batteries.
往这边移一点 这就对了
Un poquito mas aca. Es perfecto all.
很好 棒极了
Ay, good. Bellissimo.
这里怎么有个盒子
Why is this box here?!
实在抱歉 是我们放的
I am sorry -- we did,
因为我们要搬桌子
because we were moving the tables.
那你为啥要搬桌子
Well, why are you moving the tables?
这样孩子们就有更大的空间跳舞了
So the kids have more space to dance.
这样更好
It's better this way.
真的吗 歌洛莉亚
Is it really, Gloria?
因为现在这里看起来就是
Because right now it kind of just looks like
一堆桌子和一大片空地
a clump of tables and a big open space.
听着 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry,
但是我们以前就这么做的
but we've always done it this way,
我认为如果你把桌子搬来搬去
and I think it's gonna throw people off
会把人们吓跑的
if you move them around.
天啊 这些桌子看上去真不错
Oh, my god, these tables look great!
谁弄的
Who did this?
是我耶
I did!
爱死了
I love it!
你好啊
Hello.
咱们还没自我介绍呢
We haven't been properly introduced.
-我叫歌洛莉亚 -我叫贝瑟妮
- I'm Gloria. - I'm Bethenny.
不知是否有人跟你说过
I don't know if anybody's ever told you this,
你很漂亮
but you're really pretty.
不 不 贝瑟妮 没人跟她这么说过
No. No, Bethenny. No one's ever told her that.
这些桌子真超乎
I am seriously freaking out
我的想象
about these tables!
这样好了 我们在要放桌子的地方
You know what? Let's just put a pin in
做个记号
where we're gonna put the tables.
好啊 桌子就这样放
Yes, we're keeping the tables!
还有什么需要我帮忙么
So what else can I do?
你可以
Um...you can...
帮我拿一下凳子
help me with the chairs.
好吧
Okay.
我们需要很多凳子
We need a lot of them.
凳子就放在台下 就在这儿
They're under the stage right...here.
请吧
There you go.
这里还真是又黑又脏的说
It's like dirty and dark there, no?
我知道 不太爽是吧
Yeah, I know. Bummer, right?
进去吧
Off you go.
味道有点怪啊 克莱尔
Smells funny, Claire!
对不住了 继续往里爬
So sorry. Keep goin'!
又咋了嘛
What?
我们真的需要凳子
We needed chairs.
你们讲啥呢
What are you guys talking about?
没啥 他说
No, nothing. He was just saying
他爱死这些桌子了
how much he loves the tables.
要是我有收据
If I had the receipt,
我就用不着叫你查了
I wouldn't need you to look it up.
照这样下去 第一轮舞我是跳不成了
At this rate, I'm going to miss the first dance...
我说的是我以后的婚礼
at my wedding!
他不是说他只有一件东西要买单吗
I thought he only had one item.
跟你老爹说去 要是当初听我的
Tell your dad, if it were up to me,
我们十分钟之内就可以买完走人了
we'd have been in and out of here in about 10 minutes.
你说过了
You mentioned that.
我可能还会再说一次
And I'll probably mention it again,
因为托某人的福
because, thanks to someone,
我们还得继续耗在这儿
we're gonna be here for a while.
好吧 我懂了
Yeah, I get it.
知道吗 卢克 你应该买套大号的西服
You know, Luke, you should order that suit in a larger size,
因为等我们结账走人的时候[卢克该长大了] -我懂了
- because by the time we get out of here - I...get...it.
这是西装钱
Pay for the suit.
你这是要去哪
Where the hell are you going?
卢克还需要 袜子
Luke needs...socks.
要青色的
Make 'em teal!
你是承心惹我哈
You're playing a very dangerous game.
嘿 筒子们
Hey, boys...
看看谁来了
look who it is --
那个占了我们停车位的家伙
the guy that stole our parking spot.
-你要去扁他么 -是我的话就肯定扁他
- Are you going to hit him? - I'd totally hit him.
我不会扁他
I'm not gonna hit him,
但我要跟他讲道理
but I'm gonna give him a piece of my mind.
筒子们 注意了 要想当爷们儿
Now, boys, pay attention -- you want to be men,
就得学我这样对付这些痞子
this is how you handle a jerk like this.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, chief?
你今天抢了我们的停车位
You know, you stole our parking space today.
-啥 -就是这么回事
- What? - That's right.
我正在等停车位
I was waiting for the parking space,
你溜过去就把位给占了
You sneaked right in there --
你以为你爸李刚啊
that make you feel like a big man?
有吗 我根本没注意到
Did I? I didn't even notice.
这借口没啥说服力
That's no excuse.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我的狗今天死了
My dog died today.
我不得不给他安乐死
I had to put him to sleep.
十四年了
14 years,
我们俩相依为命
he was all I had.
现在我每每想起回家
Now I can't stand the thought
就独守空巢 眼泪就哗哗的
of going back to my empty apartment,
所以我就不停地跑商场来晃悠
So I just keep wandering around the mall.
这样好了 忘了
You know what? Forget about the...
停车位[也指"圆点"]的事吧
spot.
天啊
Oh, god!
他名字就是圆点
That was his name!
请不要扁他
Do not hit him.
喷点男士香水
Oasis for men?
有意思
That's funny.
你好像是在问我
You made that sound like a question,
却又不给我机会回答
then you didn't wait for me to answer.
-什么 -让哥教教你
- What? - Here, let me show you.
看 你是这么说的
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You go --
你说 喷点 男士香水
You go, "Oasis for men"?
懂不 你说了 喷点 男士香水
You see what I mean? You went, "Oasis for men"?
你应该说 要喷点男士香水吗
You should have said, "Oasis for men"?
然后我回答 给哥来两下
Then I'd go, "Yeah, give me two".
但是你说 喷点 男士香水
But instead, you went, "Oasis for men".
-好吧 -你滴明白
- Okay. I get it. - You see what I mean?
-明白了 -我看未必
- I-I get it. I get it. - No, I'm not sure you do!
你没说完“男士香水”就喷我
You sprayed before "Men"!
你说 喷点 男士香水
You went, "Oasis for men".
-好好好 -叫你喷
- Okay. Okay. - Men!
-我喷 -别闹了
- Men! Men! - Stop it! Stop it!
-我再喷 -求你了
- Men! Men! Men! Men! - Stop it!
-我继续喷 -不要啊
我喷 我喷 我喷喷喷
Men! Men! Men! Men! Men!
菲尔
Hey, Phil.
我不知道我是咋了
I don't know what happened.
我就
I just...
我
I...
我真的不知道
I don't know what happened.
我今天对你是有点小苛刻
Look, I might've come down on you a little bit hard today.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我记得我假装去买袜子
I remember pretending to go look for some socks...
是我错了
I mean, it's, uh, my fault.
我把你惹急了
I pushed your buttons.
我老丈人以前也这么对我
My father-in-law was the same way with me.
那糟老头真可怕
He was horrible.
卢卡斯外公吗 他是大好人呀
Grandpa Lucas? He was a sweetheart.
中风以后他才良心发现
Yeah, after the stroke mellowed him out good.
那之前 简直不是人啊
Before? An animal.
卢克这名字就是为了纪念他的
We named Luke after him.
我做啥都错
Everything I did was wrong.
我说白 他非得说黑
If I said it was white, he'd say it was black.
尽管他从不用黑色这个词
Although he never said anything was black
他是个变态的种族歧视
'cause he was a pretty big racist.
我还戴着他的表
I wear his watch.
死老头子 恨死他了
I hated him. Hated him.
我在想 我不知道
And I was thinking -- I don't know --
希望你对我不是这种感情
I don't want you to think the same way about me.
那你有想过
You ever think about maybe
对我有爱一些吗
not being a jerk to me so much?
别以为我只是针对你
Now, see, you got to stop taking that stuff personally.
我对所有人都那样
I'm like that with everybody.
我不好相处
I'm tough!
还尖酸刻薄
And...Mean.
不喜欢别人唧唧歪歪
I don't like to take guff!
也不考虑别人的感受
Or people's feelings into consideration.
好吧
Okay, okay.
我不敢说我一定是对的
I can't swear my way's the right way.
看你那副追欢卖笑 上窜下跳的熊样
I see you smiling, skipping around,
不知怎么 我有时会想
and I think sometimes -- I don't know --
男孩们像你这样
maybe the boys would be better off
也许还自在些
if they were a little bit more like you.
知道吗 跳比跑燃烧的卡路里更多
You know, skipping burns more calories than running.
那是
That's --
先说到这儿吧
We're done here.
对了
Oh, hey, listen.
那人没告诉我 你做啥坏事了
He didn't tell me, but what'd you do to that guy, huh?
给他点颜色瞧瞧了
Did you get him?
我对着他喷了点香水
Yeah, I sprayed him with cologne.
当我没问
I'm sorry I asked.
喷了很多香水呢
No, but, like, a lot of cologne.
我追着他一路小跑啊
I just, like, got way up in there.
真有你的
Good boy.
有啥发现
Did you find anything yet?
这个妈咪论坛上
Yes, there's a whole section on biting
有咬人讨论专区
on this Mommy forum.
不错 上面怎么说
Oh, good. What does it say?
我儿子咬人
Uh, "My son was biting,
我就找了个陌生人训他
so I got a stranger to yell at him”.
外人对他的训斥让他好怕怕
"Being disciplined by someone else outside the family
以后也不咬人了
scared him into stopping."
-很傻很天真 -小卡
- Idiots! - Cam!
咋滴了 我才不会雇什么刁民
What? I am not hiring some hobo
来伤我家小乖乖的心
to come over here and traumatize my child.
她已经有段不堪回首的记忆了
She's already prone to flashbacks,
你懂的
if you know what I mean.
她在越南又没参过战
Yeah, you know she didn't fight in Vietnam, right?
我不管 我不管
I don't know anything anymore.
还有啥
What else does it say?
好吧 这位楼主说
Okay, well, this one says,
我女儿咬她弟弟时
"When my daughter bit her brother,
我在她嘴里放了点胡椒
I put a pinch of pepper in her mouth".
她哭个不停 不过从此再不咬人了
"She cried and cried, but she never bit again".
还有个笑脸表情
Smiley face.
这笑得还有理了
Oh, well, the smiley face makes it okay.
给我囡囡一点小惩罚
"I waterboarded our toddler --
哇咔咔
lol"!
那你说 我们怎么办
Well, all right, what do you suggest we do?
退出这个西班牙知道网
That we log off the Spanish inquisition website
用爱来感化她
and handle this with love.
听我唱 莉莉
Okay, Lily...
咬一口苹果 咬一口梨
take a bite of an apple, take a bite of a pear
咬一口面前的小曲奇
take a bite of the cookie that you left over there
有些东西你不能咬
Here's one thing you should never do.
泰勒 布兰登 苏小小
Don't bite Taylor or Brandon or Sue
人不能咬呀 人不能咬
because people aren't food. People aren't food
你咬了朋友
Your friends will run away
他们就会被吓跑
if they're scared of being chewed
再给一句小忠告
and as a side note,
私密部位保护好
private parts are private
你真贤惠 问题解决了
Well...problem solved.
我知道你在挖苦我
I know you're being sarcastic,
你懂啥 还没结束呢
but you don't know that it's not.
哎哟 我的乖乖哟
Ow! Honey.
-她又咬你了吗 -没有
- Did she just bite you again? - No.
我受够了 我去拿胡椒来
That is it. I am getting the pepper!
不 你不能拿
N -- no, you are not.
小卡 这么宠她对她没好处
Cam, you're not doing her any favors by being soft.
干脆你也甭拿胡椒了
Oh, well, then, why don't you just skip the pepper,
我去找钳子 咱俩速度拔掉她的牙
I'll get some pliers, and we'll pull her teeth now!
淡定 不就是个调味品吗
Play relax! It's a seasoning.
要不你尝一个
Okay. Well, then, why don't you try some?
-别闹了 -来嘛
- Stop. - No. Try a little.
-小卡 别这样 -尝一个嘛
- Stop it. Stop it, Cam. Stop it. - No, try a little bit.
你还敢打我 看我不塞你嘴里
Don't you hit me. Here. Put some in there.
-不要 -你咬我
- No! Well... - Ow! You bit me! Mm!
你为什么不为我唱首关于这个的歌
Why don't you sing me a song about it?
看你俩的领带多搭啊
Oh, look at you two in your matching ties!
-别跟我提这事 -过来
- Don't get me started. - Ohh, come here.
卢克 亲爱的 你喷古龙水了吗
Luke, sweetie, aryou wearing cologne?
没有 老爸攻击了推销香水的家伙
No. Dad attacked the perfume guy
又拥抱了我
and then hugged me.
我看到男孩们穿着可爱的西装
I saw the boys in those adorable little suits,
然后我意识到这舞台就是他们的
and it made me realize this dance is about them.
与我无关
It's not about me
与我跟歌洛莉亚之间
and my petty little competition with...
小小的竞争无关
with Gloria.
看那边的墙
Just look at the walls in here.
谁穿成那样参加儿童舞会啊
Who wears that to a kids' dance?
没错 她看起来太赞了
I know. She looks amazing.
好了 我要用首怀旧老歌
Okay, I'm gonna slow things down
为我们的女伴们
with a blast from the past
舒缓下节奏
for our chaperones.
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
没事 我没事
No, I'm fine.
我 我没事
I'm -- I'm fine.
我没事 我没事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
我要纸巾
I need a paper towel.
不好意思 我没看见你
I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
是啊
No...
你当然没看见我了 当然了
Of course you didn't. Of course you didn't.
因为这是歌洛莉亚之夜
'Cause it's gloria's night.
没错
That's right.
全是关于歌洛莉亚 歌洛莉亚
It's all about Gloria, Gloria, Gloria!
你谈够情说够爱以后
When you're done getting married...
就把这地方拖干净点
maybe you can mop this up a little.
她怎么了
What was that?
都是这该死的制服
It's this damn uniform.
好吧 我们得谈谈
Okay, we need to talk.
不 我很好 我不需要谈
No. I am fine. I do not need to talk.
你这星期一直在排斥我
Well, you've been pushing me away the whole week.
你一直反对我的意见
You've been fighting all my ideas.
因为这是我的事 歌洛莉亚
That's because this is my thing, Gloria.
为什么不能也是我的事 克莱尔
Why can't it be my thing, too, Claire?
因为所有的事都与你有关
Because everything is your thing!
这是唯一一件我自己的事
This -- this is the one thing that was my thing.
这是我唯一的事
This is my only thing.
我的天 这是我唯一的事
Oh my god, this is my only thing.
然后你穿着你的紧身裙过来
And then you come along and you steal my thunder
用你那些很棒的主意 抢了我的风头
with your tight dresses and your great ideas.
我是那个受到所有妈妈尊敬的人
I was the one that all the moms looked up to.
我是格斯唯一喜欢的人
I was the only one that Gus liked.
拜托
Ay! Please.
你那么喜欢他 你可以留着他
You like him so much, you can keep him.
现在不一样了 我知道他喜欢你
It's not the same now that I know he likes you.
这听上去真的很疯
That sounds really insane,
但这跟格斯没关系
but this isn't actually about gus.
是吗 因为你一直在谈论他
Really? Because you've been talking a lot about him.
歌洛莉亚 格斯只是一个符号
Gloria, Gus is a symbol.
性符号吗
A sex symbol?
别说了 歌洛莉亚 我都哭了
Stop it, Gloria. I'm already crying.
克莱尔 我不是来这儿抢你风头的
Claire...I didn't come here to steal your thunder.
你的就是你的
Your thunder is your thunder,
我的就是我的
and my thunder is my thunder.
我知道 只是上帝给你的比较多
I know. It's just that god gave you so much thunder.
可能是有点太多了
Yeah, maybe too much.
我讨厌那些女人看我的眼神
I hate how those women look at me.
你以为我不知道她们是怎么想的吗
You think I don't know what they're thinking?
哟 来了个性感的波霸
"Ah, here comes the hot one with the big boobies
搞不好会抢了我老公
that is gonna steal my husband".
也许她们都不会让自己的孩子跟曼尼玩
And maybe they don't let their kids play with Manny.
我自愿来这是因为我想让他们看看
I volunteer because I want them to see
我还有更多其他的内涵
that there's so much more to me.
你为什么没跟我说过这些
Why didn't you tell me that?
也许就跟你没告诉我
Maybe for the same reason you didn't tell me
你对格斯有奇怪的感觉一样
you had a weird thing for Gus --
这很尴尬的
It's embarrassing.
好吧 我很抱歉
Okay. I am sorry.
我把整件事
I made this whole thing
变成了可笑的竞争
into some ridiculous competition,
而且 我真可悲
and...I'm pathetic.
你不可悲
You're not pathetic.
好吧 是有点令人难过
Okay, that's a little bit sad.
我们喜欢自认为聪明
We like to think we're so smart
自认为自己能解决一切问题
and we have all the answers.
而且我们希望可以把这些传授给孩子们
And we want to pass all that on to our children.
但是
But...
如果你不只停留在肤浅的表面上的话
if you scratch beneath the surface,
用不着深究就能看到你自己儿时的样子
you don't have to dig very deep to find the kid you were.
这也正是疯狂的地方
Which is why it's kind of crazy
现在我们自己都有孩子了
that now we're raising kids of our own.
你知道吗 这是一个里程碑
You know what? This is a milestone.
我们接受我们的小天使并不是那么完美
We're accepting that our little angel isn't perfect.
是的 这没关系
That's right. And it's okay.
我 我收回刚才的话
I-I take it back --
她很完美
she is perfect.
但是我猜这才是生命真正的轮回
But I guess that's the real circle of life.
你父母这样长大
Your parents faked their way through it,
你也这样长大
you fake your way through it,
那么 我希望
and, hopefully,
你没有养了一个连环杀人犯
you don't raise a serial killer.
这不好笑
That's not funny.
我感到很抱歉
I am so sorry.
不 把所有事都抛在脑后
No,just come over watching movie
过来看电影吧
put the whole thing behind you.
好的 一会见
Okay, see you in a bit.
是浪琴 他现在心情很差
That was Longines. He's in a very bad place.
不是吧 怎么了
Oh, no. What happened?
有个疯子在商场发飙了
Well, apparently some maniac went crazy at the mall
用男士香水袭击了他
and attacked him with oasis for men.
好吧 我想我们都知道早晚会有这么一天
Oh. Well, I think we all knew that day was coming.
好吧 祝我好运
All right. Wish me luck.
祝你好运
Good luck.
好了 亲爱的
Okay, honey.
拜托不要咬老爸
Please don't hurt daddy.
好了
All right.
来 张嘴
"Ahh".